Alright, this is a very important video, please watch it and please share it.
Before that, let me tell you two important things about UPI.
UPI doesn't allow you to transact only 20 transactions or 1 lakh rupees a day.
Now this limit gets hit quickly and we can't transact after that.
Second important thing, if you know a little about banking automation,
then you should know that if you have a little mistake in your name in the bank and in the system,
then the transaction fails.
Why am I telling you all this?
Because in our affiliates there are all these issues.
So I thought I should address all these issues to you.
Why did the payment fail and how are we handling the payments manually?
So the first thing is that our tea code affiliates are only in India and we only pay in India.
So please don't try it or don't try it.
This is only for India.
The second important thing is that we saw that some people, many people in fact,
made some mistakes in their name.
Your name can be in banking.
Some are starting from Mr. or Mrs.
Many people have made a lot of mistakes in the last name.
Just like your name is in the bank, write exactly the same name.
In the caps, write the caps as well.
But still, don't take the risk.
Write the name as it is.
Because the UPI transaction limit is only 1 lakh and 20 transactions end quickly.
And when there are so many mistakes and failures, then the automatic payment of the razor cannot be paid.
So we are paying a lot of money manually.
But obviously, it will take time because the payments are enough and there are banking limits.
So my humble request is that you should go to the account.
Check your bank again.
Bank account number, IFSC code.
Other than that, your name is exactly the same as in the past book.
Same last name, exactly the same.
Otherwise, the payment fails and you don't get the payment on time.
What happens with that?
When so many webhooks fail,
the razor often stops us from paying.
Then we have to do the transaction process again.
Which is very painful and you can't get the payment on time.
So please, it is a humble request.
Go to the system once and check.
All things should be accurate.
And the rest we are doing.
We will take a few more weeks because we are paying manually and the limit gets hit.
So whatever time it takes, it will take.